Russia
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Russia
2.1.1.1.24
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1239
- Russia, 2.1.1.1.24
  - Guard and Frank R. Roberson in the Kremlin, Moscow, 1913; 23; 2400; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Interior of Kremlin, Moscow, 1913; 24; 2401; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Gate and Kremlin, Moscow, 1913; 25; 2402; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Guard in the Kremlin, Moscow, 1913; 26; 2403; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Beggars in the Kremlin, Moscow, 1913; 27; 2404; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Woman begging, Moscow, 1913; 28; 2405; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Thieves market, Moscow, 1913; 29; 2406; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - The Kremlin from across the river, Moscow, 1913; 30; 2407; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson in Moscow at Trinity Gate, 1913; 31; 2408; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Pilgrim at statue of Alexander II, Moscow, 1913; 32; 2409; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - The big bell, the Kremlin, Moscow, 1913; 33; 2410; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Ward in foundling hospital, Moscow, 1913; 34; 2411; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Cab with pheumatic tires, Moscow, 1913; 35; 2412; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Red Square with Church of Saint Basil, Moscow, 1913; 36; 2413; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Holy Gate and Convent of the Ascension, in the Kremlin, Moscow, 1913; 37; 2414; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Church of Our Savior and Alexander III memorial, Moscow, 1913; 38; 2415; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Church of Ivan the Great, the Kremlin, Moscow, 1913; 39; 2416; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Cross marking the spot where Grand Duke Serge fell, the Kremlin, Moscow, 1913; 40; 2417; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Ward in the foundling hospital, Moscow, 1913; 41; 2418; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - The foundling hospital, Moscow, 1913; 42; 2419; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Memorial to Alexander III, Moscow, 1913; 43; 2420; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Nurse in the foundling hospital, Moscow, 1913; 44; 2421; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Street in new business section, Moscow, 1913; 45; 2422; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Interior of arcade, Moscow, 1913; 46; 2423; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Church of Ivan Velki and captured canon, the Kremlin, Moscow, 1913; 47; 2424; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Two nurses, foundling hospital, Moscow, 1913; 48; 2425; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - The Holy Gate, taken from the Red Square, Moscow, 1913; 49; 2426; 5x7 (Box 1239)
  - Showing cupola of Greek church, Moscow, 1913; 50; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - His Imperial Majesty Nikolai Aleksandrovich [Nicholas II], copy, 1913; 51; 2X; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Man in military uniform, copy, 1913; 52; 4X; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Man in military uniform, copy, 1913; 53; 5X; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Grand Duchesses Olga, Tatiana, Anastasia and Maria with the Tsarevich Alexei, children of Tsar Nicholas II, copy, 1913; 54; 6X; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Emperor Nicholas Aleksandrovich [Nicholas II], copy, 1913; 55; 8X; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Tsarevich Alexei Nikolaevich Romanov, copy, 1913; 56; 9X; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  - Her Imperial Majesty, Empress Alexandra Gosudarynya Feodorovna, copy, 1913; 57; 11X; 4x5 (Box 1239)
  Box 1240
- Russia, 2.1.1.1.24
  - Her Imperial Majesty, Empress Alexandra Gosudarynya Feodorovna, copy, 1913; 1; 13X; 4x5 (Box 1240)
  - Her Imperial Majesty, Empress Alexandra Gosudarynya Feodorovna, copy, 1913; 2; 15X; 4x5 (Box 1240)
  - The Kremlin, Moscow, copy, 1913; 3; 24X; 4x5 (Box 1240)
  - Boy with stick, copy, 1913; 4; 25 X; 4x5 (Box 1240)
  - Kupalschitsa, copy, 1913; 5; 28X; 4x5 (Box 1240)
  - Mihail Aleksandrovich, copy, 1913; 6; 41X; 4x5 (Box 1240)
  - His Royal Majesty, Emperor Alexander III, copy, 1913; 7; 42X; 4x5 (Box 1240)
  - Boy sitting at desk, copy, 1913; 8; 44X; 4x5 (Box 1240)
  - At the door of the school, copy, 1913; 9; 45X; 4x5 (Box 1240)
  - County Tolstoy, copy, before 1916; 10; 5x7 (Box 1240)
  - County Tolstoy, copy, before 1916; 11; 5x7 (Box 1240)